<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>IACHR hearing on freedom of expression</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/hearing-iachr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/hearing-iachr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Different civil society organizations, union representatives and delegates of the Argentine State participated on November 19 in the hearing on the situation of freedom of expression in Argentina convened by the Inter-American Commission on Human Rights. The session is the result of two requests promoted by civil society organizations, academia and experts. CELE was one of the organizations that supported the request made by the Argentine Journalism Forum (FOPEA).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The participating organizations denounced a rapid and pronounced deterioration in the conditions for journalistic practice in Argentina.  They pointed out a significant increase in attacks against journalists, ranging from internet violence and harassment to physical violence, and many times carried out by public authorities. CELE had already highlighted and analyzed this situation, also noted in the most recent report of the Office of the Special Rapporteur for Freedom of Expression (RELE) of the Inter-American Commission on Human Rights.  FOPEA described as “narratives of hate and misinformation” the ongoing patterns of attacks by public government officials, used strategically for silencing through the restriction of public debate, especially by President Javier Milei, who stated, on repeated occasions, that “we do not hate journalists enough.”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
